ACTWU's Social Services Department Records 5619/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Amalgamated Chicago Group Employees Pension Plan, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  May 6
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, General Executive Board Minutes, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Alaska, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Committees, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- ACTOR, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Allied Industrial Workers of America, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- American Income Life Insurance, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  July 6
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Council, Campaign financing, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  July 31
- Miscellaneous, 1956-1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Civil Rights Committee, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Clay Civil Rights, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  1 photograph
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Dues, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Council Recommendations, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Staff, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Amalgamate Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Charter Revision New York City, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Chicago- Joint Board, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Chicago Principals Association, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Chicago Amalgamated Social Benefits Association, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Chicago-Social Benefits, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Child Abuse, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Child Care, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Child Care, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Child Care, 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Child Care Action Campaign, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Child Care Legislation, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Child Labor, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Child Labor Coalition, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Children's Clarion Rights Project, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Children's Defense Fund, 1977-1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Child Health, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Children's Summit (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Children's Vigil, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Chile, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- China, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Citizens Committee For Immigration Reform, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Citizens Congress on National Security, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Citizens for Tax Justice, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- City Volunteer Corporation, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Civil Rights Act, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Civil Rights Committee Designee's, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Civil Rights Mailings, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Civil Rights Meeting; Atlanta, Georgia, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Civil rights meeting: Fontaine Bleau, Miami Beach, Florida, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Civil Rights Meeting: Atlanta Georgia, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Civil Rights Meeting: Linthicum Heights, Maryland, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Civil Rights Meeting: Atlanta, Georgia, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Civil Rights Conference: St. Louis, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Civil Rights [1 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Civil Rights Survey, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Civil Rights [2 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Civil Rights Reports, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Civil Rights Breakdown, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Civil Rights Breakdown, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Clean Air, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Cleaners and Dyers (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Clinton Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Clinton Budget (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Clinton Campaign, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Clinton Economic Plan, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Clothing Industry, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  September
- Clothing Negotiations, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, General, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Cluett, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Coal Industry-Women, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Coalition For Amtrak Revitalization Car, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Coalition for Children and Youth, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Coalition for Democratic Values, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Coalition for Employment through Exports, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Coalition for Women's Appointments, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Collective Bargaining, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- College Information (Box 13, Folder 34)
- College of New Rochelle, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Columbia Disability Project, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Columbia University-Immigration Policy, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Columbia University, 1975-1986 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Commission on the Status of Women, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Committee for Economic Development, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Committee for National Health Service (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Committee for National Security, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Committee for the Third Sector, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Communications Workers of America, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Community Council of Greater New York -Health Care Task Force, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Community Council of Greater New York -Task Force on Adequate Income and Services, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Community Reinvestment Act, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  May 21
- Community Service: American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1976-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Community Service Society, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Consumer Credit - National Foundation, 1975-1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Consumer Coalition for Health, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Consumer, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- U.S. Constitution Bi-Centennial, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Conservatism Program, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  January 10
- Connecticut State American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Connecticut State Labor Council, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  April 5
- Congress, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Congratulations - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Conference on Families, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Conference on Economic Progress, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  January 25
- Conference Board, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Competitiveness Policy Council, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Comparable Worth Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Comparable Worth Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Comparable Worth Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Comparable Worth, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Comparable Worth, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Comparable Worth, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Comparable Worth, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Comparable Worth, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Council on Municipal Performance, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Community Union Project New Jersey, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Community Services Society Juvenile Justice, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Community Service Society Committee on Aging, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Community Service Firms of New York, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Community Service Society of New York, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Cornell Course- Joyce, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Cornell [1 of 2], 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Cornell [2 of 2], 1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Cornell - New York School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1975-1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Cornell - Industrial and Labor Relations Advisory Council, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Cornell - Center Women Policy Studies, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Copenhagen Conference, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Committee on Political Education - Texas, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  August 23
- Committee on Political Education, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Cooperative Insurance, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  May 15
- Cooperative Extension, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Convention Resolutions (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Cooperative Education, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  July 9
- Convention - 1996, 1987-1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Convention - 1993, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Convention, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Convention Group Specialists, 1977-1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Contract - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Office, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Contingent Workers, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Consumers Union, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  May 20
- Consumer Tax Alliance, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Consumer Protection, 1973-1978 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Consumer Federation, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Consumer Education, 1977-1986 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Cost Containment - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Cotton Garment Agreement, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Cotton Garment, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  November 14
- Cotton Garment, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Cotton Garment, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Cotton Garment Contract, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Cotton Garment Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Cotton Garment, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Cotton Garment, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Cotton Garment Shirts, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Cotton Garment Outerwear, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Cotton Garment Pants, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  July 8
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Cotton Garment Insurance, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Council for the Aged - Lower west side inter-agency, 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Council on Foreign Relations, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Council on Social Work Education, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Council on Social Education, 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Council on Social Work Education - Fund Raising, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Council on Social Work Education - Sub Committee, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Credit, 1978-1991 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Credit Problems - Extensions, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Credit Unions, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Crime, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Cuba, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- CUNY - Citizens Committee for Public Accountability in the Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Cyprus, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Daily News Strike, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Day Care - Federal Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Day Care Food Service, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  March 2
- Day Care Fund, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  February 21
- Day Care - National, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Day Care - Baltimore JT. BD., 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Day Care - Chicago, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Day Care - Kentucky, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  February 9
- Day Care - Nebraska, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Day Care - New York, 1973-1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Day Care Nutrition, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Day Care - Ohio, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Day Care - St. Louis, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Day Care - Research (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Day Care - Texas, 1971-1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Debs Foundation, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Defense, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  February 28
- Delinquency, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Democracy, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  April 24
- Democratic Agenda, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Democratic Convention, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Democratic Convention, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Democratic Convention, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Democratic Left, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Democratic National Committee, 1982-1987 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Democratic Party, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  May 30
- Democratic Planning Group, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  March 15
- Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Democrats for Choice, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  March 12
- Department Head Meetings, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  February 22
- Department of Labor, 1977-1989 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Department of Labor Plant Closings, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  January 31
- Department of Professional Employees - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Diana De Pugh, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Detroit, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  May 29
- Dinkins Campaign, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Dinkins Campaign, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Disabled, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Disabled Children Project, 1983-1987 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Discharge, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Dislocated Workers, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- District 65, 1974-1986 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Dole Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Dream Continues - Film, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Drug Abuse, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Eastern Strike, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Drug Testing, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Drug Testing, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Duty of Fair Representation, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  October 10
- Earned Income Tax Credit, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Earth Day, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Ebert Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Economic Adjustment and Work Dislocation, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Eastern Europe, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Economic Opportunity Act, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  June 12
- Economic Policy Council, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Economic Policy Institution, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  August 3
- Economic Think Tank (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Economics, 1974-1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- The Economy, 1975-1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Education, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Education Department/Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Education Fund - Chicago Joint Board, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Education Higher, 1972-1977 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Education Plan, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Education Plan - Local 169, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Education - Scholarship Programs Amalgamated and Textile, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  January 13
- Education Union (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Education Challenges, Incorporated, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Item 807, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  April 1
- Egypt, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  February 14
- Elder Care, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Local 1199 - Hospital Workers, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- 1199 Cultural Center, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- El Salvador, 1983-1989 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Emergency Aid Fund, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  February 5
- Employee Benefits Task Force, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  May
- Employment, 1972-1992 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Employment of People with Disabilities, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Energy Coalition, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Energy Crisis, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Enforcement Committee, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- England, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  February 4
- Enterprise Zones, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  February 26
- Environment (Ecology), 1979-1992 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1972-1980 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1973-1981 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Equal Pay Act, 1977-1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Equal Rights Amendment - 1983, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Equal Rights Amendment #2, 1975-1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Equal Rights Amendment, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Equal Rights Amendment - America, 1976-1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Equal Rights Amendment Boycott, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Equal Rights Amendment - Extension, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Equal Rights Amendment - Illinois, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Equal Rights Amendment - New York State, 1975-1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Equal Rights Amendment - Virginia, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Equal Worth Conference, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Employee Retirement Income Security Act (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Employee stock ownership program, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  January 23
- Ethiopia, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  January 3
- Eurosocialism and America, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Evolution of Work - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Evolution of Work Committee Meeting, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Excise Tax, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Executive Council, American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Executive Pay, 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Exports, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Export Council, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Family Issues - Leave, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Family Planning, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Farah, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Farmworkers, 1973-1981 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Fasanella, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Fast Track, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Federal Communications Commission, 1983-1990 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Federal Disability, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  November 1
- Federal Education Project, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  January 30
- Federal Woman's Award, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Federally Employed Women, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  April 25
- Federationist - Article (Box 19, Folder 34)
- International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, Professional and Technical Employees (FIET), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Films - Lists, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Financial Democracy, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Finley, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Finley, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Finley Dinner, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Finley Dinner, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Finley - Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  6 Photographs
- Finley - Video, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Flexitime, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Florio Campaign, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Food, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Ford Foundation, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Foreign Born, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Foreign Policy, 1975-1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Foreign Visitors, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  April 27
- Foundations, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR), 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Fourteen B, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- 14th Street Union Square Area Project, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Miriam Friedlander, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Fromm Institute for Lifelong Learning, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Friedrich - Ebert - Stiftung, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Friends of A. Philip Randolph, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Frontlash, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Farah Student - FrontLash, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Full Employment, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1976-1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Funerals, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  November 30
- Future of the Union, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Future of Work (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Gateway Program, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- General Executive Board, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  5 Photographs
- Philadelphia General Executive Board, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board [1 of 2], 1989 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board [2 of 2], 1989 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  November
- General Executive Board [1 of 2], 1987 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  1 Photograph
- General Executive Board [2 of 2], 1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board [1 of 2], 1986 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- General Executive Board [2 of 2], 1986 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- General Executive Board, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- General Joint Board Information, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- General Office - Staff Education, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1977-1992 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- German Marshall Fund, 1985-1989 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- German Marshall Fund, 1982-1985 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- German Marshall Fund, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- German Marshall Fund, Equal Opportunity Internship Candidates, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- German Marshall Fund Internship Committee, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Germany, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Germany - Women, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Girls Clubs of America, 1975-1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Girls Clubs Board Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Girls Clubs Labor Committee, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  June 2
- Girls Club Manchester, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Girls Clubs - Social Concerns, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Global Economy (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Gloversville, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  January 17
- Lee Goldberg, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Good Housekeeping, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Gottfried Bill, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Government (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Government Ethics (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Government Industrial Commission, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Graduate Student, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  August 8
- Gramm - Rudman, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Grants, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- National Commission of Working Women, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  November 21
- Grant - CUW - New York City, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Grant Disability, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Grant - Disabled (Government), 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  2 Photographs
- Grant Disability [1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Grant Disability [2 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Grant Handicapped, 1977-1983 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Handicapped Grant - Labor Issues (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Working Paper Affirmative Action for the Disabled, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Government Grant Staff Reports (Disabled), 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Grant - Shoe Workers, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Gray Panthers, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Greece, 1983-1987 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Gun Control (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Guatemala, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Guttman Institution (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Haiti, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Hall of Fame - Labor International, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- The Handicapped, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Harvard Labor Law School, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Health Assistance Program, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Health Care, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Health Care, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Health Centers, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Health Hazards, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Health Insurance, 1973-1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Health Law, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Winter
- Health Services Network Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  August 13
- Women Office Workers, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Health, Welfare, and Pension Education Conference, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Clark Herman Project, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Sidney Hillman Biographies and Letters, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center, 1975-1985 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Hirsch Campaign, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Hispanics, 1985-1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Histadrut, 1973-1990 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Holocaust Museum, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Home Care Workers, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Homeless, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Homemaker Services National, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Homework Ban, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Hormel, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Hospital Cost Containment Clothing, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  January 26
- Hospital Workers Union 1199, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Hotels - Union Properties, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  May 2
- Household Workers, 1974-1983 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Housing, 1974-1992 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Housing now, 1985-1989 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Help through Industry Retraining and Employment (HIRE), 1977 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Human Contract - S-S. Leo Perlis, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Human Resource Development Institute, 1978-1991 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Human Rights, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  March 24